Tissue Culture Association records
Tissue Culture Association records
- Series III. Treasurer, 1947-1980; 1300 items (2 linear feet)
  - Correspondence/Hink: Business Office 1976-1979 (Box 14, Folder 48)
  - Correspondence/Hink: Taxes 1978 (Box 14, Folder 49)
  - Annual Report (Secretary-Treasurer) 1953-1955, 1957 (Box 14, Folder 50)
  - Annual Report (Secretary-Treasurer) 1958, 1959 (Box 14, Folder 51)
  - Annual Report (Secretary-Treasurer) 1960-1962 (Box 14, Folder 52)
  - Annual Report (Secretary-Treasurer) 1962-1964 (Box 14, Folder 53)
  - Annual Report (Secretary-Treasurer) 1965-1969, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 54)
  - Audits 1968-1972 (Box 14, Folder 55)
  - Audits 1973-1976 (Box 14, Folder 56)
  - Audits 1977 (Box 14, Folder 57)
  - Audits 1978 (Box 14, Folder 58)
  - Audits 1982 (Box 14, Folder 59)
  - Bank Statements 1979 (Box 14, Folder 60)
  - Budget (undated) (Box 14, Folder 61)
  - Budget 1970 (Box 14, Folder 62)
  - Budget 1971 (Box 14, Folder 63)
  - Budget 1972 (Box 14, Folder 64)
  - Budget 1973 (Box 14, Folder 65)
  - Budget 1979 (Box 14, Folder 66)
  - Budget (in Vitro) 1971 (Box 14, Folder 67)
  - Budget 1979 (Box 14, Folder 68)
  - Budget /Proposed 1968-1970 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Budget/Proposed 1971-1973 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Budget/Proposed 1974, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Budget/Proposed 1975-1976 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Budget/Proposed 1978-1980 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Budget/Reviews 1969-1972 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Budget/Summary 1972 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Budget/Summary 1973 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Budget/Summary 1974 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Budget/Summary 1975 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Budget/Summary 1976 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Budget/Summary 1977 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Budget/Summary 1978 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Budget/Summary 1979 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Business Meeting Minutes and Report 1963 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Cash Receipts 1977-1979 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Disbursements 1979-1980 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Expenses/Education Committee 1978 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Expenses/Meeting 1979 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Expenses/Meeting Executive Board 1979 (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - Expenses/Meeting Program Committee (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Expenses/Paid 1978-1979 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - Expenses/Reimbursement Requests 1978-1979 (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - Expenses/reimbursement Requests 1979 (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - Financial Reports 1949-1956 (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - Financial Reports 1958-1966 (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - Financial Reports 1967 (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - Financial Reports 1968-1972 (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - Financial Reports 1973 (Box 15, Folder 29)
  - Financial Reports 1976-1977 (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - Financial Reports 1978-1979 (Box 15, Folder 31)
  - Financial Reports 1980 (Box 15, Folder 32)
  - Financial Summaries 1950-1965 (Box 15, Folder 33)
  - Forms (Box 15, Folder 34)
  - Income Anticipated 1973 (Box 15, Folder 35)
  - Ledger 1977-1979 (Box 15, Folder 36)
  - Michigan Branches 1978-1980 (Box 15, Folder 37)
  - Monies Invested 1974 (Box 15, Folder 38)
  - Reports/Charitable Organizations 1976 (Box 15, Folder 39)
  - Reports/Lake Placid Project 1968 (Box 15, Folder 40)
  - Reports/Local Committee 1976, 1978, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 41)
  - Reports/Meeting 1962 (Box 15, Folder 42)
  - Reports/Travel Expenses 1965-1966 (Box 15, Folder 43)
  - Requisition/Hetherington 1952-1955 (Box 15, Folder 44)
  - Research Grants and Contracts 1978 (Box 15, Folder 45)
  - Statements/Columbia University 1947-1949 (Box 15, Folder 46)
  - Summary of Accounts/Ohio State 1974/10 (Box 15, Folder 47)
  - Tax/Correspondence IRS (1965-1979) (Box 15, Folder 48)
  - Tax Exemption 1963, 1971, 1977 (Box 15, Folder 49)
  - Tax/Income 1965 (Box 15, Folder 50)
  - Tax/Income Tax Forms 1970 (Box 15, Folder 51)
  - Tax/Income Tax Forms 1972 (Box 15, Folder 52)
  - Tax/Income Tax Forms 1973-1975 (Box 15, Folder 53)
  - Tax/Income Tax Forms 1978 (Box 15, Folder 54)
  - Tax/IRS Audit 1977-1980 (Box 15, Folder 55)
- Series IV. Business Office, 1978-1984; 1000 items (1.5 linear feet)
  This series contains correspondence reports, expense sheets, tax forms, and applications and legal documents in alphabetical order by type of document followed by date order.
  - Correspondence/Executive Director (Momberger) 1978 (Box 15, Folder 56)
  - Correspondence/Executive Director (Momberger) 1979/1-5 (Box 15, Folder 57)
  - Correspondence/Executive Director (Momberger) 1979/6-12 (Box 15, Folder 58)
  - Correspondence/Executive Director (Momberger) 1980-1981 (Box 15, Folder 59)
  - Correspondence/Executive Director (Momberger) 1982-1991 (Box 15, Folder 60)
  - Disbursements and Receipts 1982 (Box 15, Folder 61)
  - Disbursements and Receipts 1983 (Box 15, Folder 62)
  - Disbursements and Receipts 1984 (Box 15, Folder 63)
  - Expenses 1978 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Federal Taxes 1980-1981 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Lease Agreement (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Maryland Taxes (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Manager Applications 1978 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Surety Bond 1978-1980 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Unemployment Insurance 1979-1980 (Box 16, Folder 7)
- Series V. Committees, 1951-1985; bulk 1969-1978; 1300 items (2 linear feet)
  Files containing correspondence, minutes, reports and memos are arranged in alphabetical order by committee title and then in date order.
  - Ad Hoc Committee/Archives (1976/7-1978/5) (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Ad Hoc Committee/ Carcinogenesis, Mutagenesis and Toxicity Testing in Vitro (1974/9-1978/5) (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Ad Hoc Committee/ Certification of Laboratory Technologists in Tissue Culture (1976/8-1978/2) (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Ad Hoc Committee/ Decennial Review Conference (1974/1-1977/2 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Ad Hoc Committee/ Chemically Defined Media (1976/7-1978/6) (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Ad Hoc Committee/ Earle Award (1976/12-1978/8) (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Ad Hoc Committee//Editorial (1976/5-1977/4) (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Ad Hoc Committee/ Endowment (1976/5-1976/8) (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Ad Hoc Committee/ Film Collection (1970-1977/1) (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Ad Hoc Committee/ International Science Fair (1976/2-1978/6) (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Ad Hoc Committee/ In Vitro Research and Human Values (1976/5-9) (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Ad Hoc Committee/ Materials and Supplies (1974/9-1977/5) (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Ad Hoc Committee/ NASA Program (1974/7-1978/7) (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Ad Hoc Committee/ Professional Management/Internal Audit (1978) (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - Ad Hoc Committee/ Publications (1971/5-1977/7) (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - Ad Hoc Committee/ Review Responsibilities of Publications Committee and Cell Science Center (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - Ad Hoc Committee/ Serum and Contamination (1974-1978/2) (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - Ad Hoc Committee/ Standardization, Collection and Distribution of Cell and Tissue (1969/11-1978/2) (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - Ad Hoc Committee/ Student Affairs (1973-1977/3) (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - Ad Hoc Committee/ Terminology (1976/5- 1978/3) (Box 16, Folder 27)
  - Ad Hoc Committee/ Training Needs/Report (1967-1968) (Box 16, Folder 28)
  - Archives (1971-1972) (Box 16, Folder 29)
  - Chemically Defined Media/ Correspondence (1969/12-1970/12) (Box 16, Folder 30)
  - Chemically Defined Media/ Correspondence/Morton (1972/1-1973/1) (Box 16, Folder 31)
  - Chemically Defined Media (1974) (Box 16, Folder 32)
  - Corrections 1974-1976 (Box 16, Folder 33)
  - Constitutions (1975/7-1977/7) (Box 16, Folder 34)
  - Contaminations in Cell and Tissue Cultures (1969-1973) (Box 16, Folder 35)
  - Contamination in Cells and Tissue Culture Report (1972) (Box 16, Folder 36)
  - Contamination in Cells and Tissue Culture Annual Report (1972) (Box 16, Folder 37)
  - Decennial Review Conference Annual Report 1976 (Box 16, Folder 38)
  - Endowment (1977-1979) (Box 16, Folder 39)
  - Endowment/ Meeting 1977 (Box 16, Folder 40)
  - Financial (1984-1985) (Box 16, Folder 41)
  - In Vitro and Human Values (1974-1976) (Box 16, Folder 42)
  - Local program (1976/11-1977/5) (Box 16, Folder 43)
  - Materials and Supplies Annual Report 1974 (Box 16, Folder 44)
  - Membership/ Correspondence ( 1975/4-1976/7) (Box 16, Folder 45)
  - Membership/ Correspondence/ Yerganian (1976/7-1977/6 (Box 16, Folder 46)
  - Members List 1974 (Box 16, Folder 47)
  - Members List 1974-1976 (Box 16, Folder 48)
  - Member Files A-K (1976-1978) (Box 16, Folder 49)
  - Member Files L-T (1976-1978) (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Member Files U-Z (1976-1978) (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Nominations/ Correspondence (1974/6-1977/2) (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Pamphlet and Film List (1951-1963) (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Program Committee/ Minutes and Reports (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Program (1975-1976) (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Program (1977) (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Program (1978) (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Public Affairs/Federation of American Societies for Experimental Biology (1970-1978) (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Publications(1974) (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Publications/ Correspondence (1968-1969) (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Publications/ Correspondence (1970-1973) (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Publications/ In Vitro (1975/5-1978/3) (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Publications/ Policies and Procedures Handbook (1974-1978) (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Publicity (1978/6-1979/1) (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Serums Reports (1971, 1973) (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Special Committee/Tissue Culture Manual (1975-1976) (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Standing (1964-1977) (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Steering (1977) (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Tissue Culture Association and Tissue Culture Commission Lists (1948-1966) (Box 17, Folder 20)
- Series VI. Branches and Divisions, 1963-1997; bulk 1968-1977; 600 items (1 linear foot)
  Files containing constitutions, by-laws, reports and correspondence are arranged in alphabetical order by section name and then in date order.
  - California (1969-1972) (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - California (1973-1975) (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - California (1976-1977) (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - California (1978) (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - Central States (1972-1978) (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - Honor Fell Division (1971-1978) (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - Invertebrate (1972-1978) (Box 17, Folder 27)
  - Michigan (1968-1975) (Box 17, Folder 28)
  - Michigan (1966-1978) (Box 17, Folder 29)
  - Midwestern (1975-1978) (Box 17, Folder 30)
  - Montreal (1977) (Box 17, Folder 31)
  - National Capital Area (1974-1987) (Box 17, Folder 32)
  - New York (1977) (Box 17, Folder 33)
  - Northeast (1977-1978) (Box 17, Folder 34)
  - Organic Culture (1970-1972) (Box 17, Folder 35)
  - Plant Division (1963-1966) (Box 17, Folder 36)
  - Plant Division (1967-1973) (Box 17, Folder 37)
  - Plant Division (1974) (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Plant Division (1975) (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Plant Division (1976-1978) (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Proposed Clubs (1974, 1977) (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Rocky Mountain (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Texas (1975-1977) (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Roster 1975-1997 (Box 18, Folder 7)
- Series VII. Meetings, 1946-1986; bulk 1947-1980; 6200 items (9.75 linear feet)
  Size: 6200 items (9.75 linear feet Files contain minutes and related materials from Executive Council and annual meetings of TCA, and materials of TCA affiliated conferences and meetings. The Series is arranged into five sub-series and then in date order by meeting date: Executive Council, Annual, Decennial Review Conference, related conferences, and audiotapes.
  - Subseries VII.A. Executive Council, 1947-1985; 2,250 items (3.5 linear feet)
    Files containing minutes, reports, agendas, memos and correspondence are arranged by meeting date and then in alphabetical order by subject.
    - Executive Council 1947 (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Executive Council 1948 (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Executive Council 1949 (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Executive Council 1950 (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - Executive Council 1951 (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - Executive Council 1952 (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - Executive Council 1953 (Box 18, Folder 14)
    - Executive Council 1954 (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - Executive Council 1955 (Box 18, Folder 16)
    - Executive Council 1956 (Box 18, Folder 17)
    - Executive Council 1957 (Box 18, Folder 18)
    - Executive Council 1958 (Box 18, Folder 19)
    - Executive Council 1959 (Box 18, Folder 20)
    - Executive Council 1960 (Box 18, Folder 21)
    - Executive Council 1961 (Box 18, Folder 22)
    - Executive Council 1962 (Box 18, Folder 23)
    - Executive Council 1963 (Box 18, Folder 24)
    - Executive Council 1964 (Box 18, Folder 25)
    - Executive Council 1965 (Box 18, Folder 26)
    - Executive Council 1966 (Box 18, Folder 27)
    - Executive Council 1967 (Box 18, Folder 28)
    - Executive Council/Minutes and Agendas 1968 (Box 18, Folder 29)
    - Executive Council/Related Documents 1968 (Box 18, Folder 30)
    - Executive Council/Correspondence (1969/1-6) Box 18 (Box 18, Folder 31)
    - Executive Council/Correspondence (1969/7-12) Box 18 (Box 18, Folder 32)
    - Executive Council/Minutes and Agenda 1969 (Box 18, Folder 33)
    - Executive Council/Minutes and Agenda 1970 (Box 18, Folder 34)
    - Executive Council/Related Materials 1970 (Box 18, Folder 35)
    - Executive Council/Minutes and Agenda 1971 (Box 18, Folder 36)
    - Executive Council/Related Materials 1971 (Box 18, Folder 37)
    - Executive Council/January 1972 (Box 18, Folder 38)
    - Executive Council/Minutes and Agenda 1972 (Box 18, Folder 39)
    - Executive Council/Minutes and Agenda 1972/6 (Box 18, Folder 40)
    - Executive Council/Minutes and Agenda 1972/10 (Box 18, Folder 41)
    - Executive Council/Related Materials 1972/10 (Box 18, Folder 42)
    - Executive Council/Related Memos 1972 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Executive Council (1973/2) (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Executive Council/Related Materials (1973/2) (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Executive Council/Budgets and Resolutions (1973/6) (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Executive Council/Minutes and Agenda (1973/6) (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Executive Council/Related Materials (1973/6) (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Executive Council/Minutes and Agenda (1973/11) (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Executive Council/Related Materials (1973/11) (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - Executive Council/Minutes and Agenda (1974/3) (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - Executive Council/Related Materials (1974/3) (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - Executive Council/Minutes and Agendas 1974/6 (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - Executive Council/Related Materials 1974/6 (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - Executive Council/Conference Call 1974/7 (Box 19, Folder 13)
    - Executive Council/Minutes and Agenda 1974/11 (Box 19, Folder 14)
    - Executive Council/Related Materials 1974/11 (Box 19, Folder 15)
    - Executive Council/Minutes and Agenda 1975/4 (Box 19, Folder 16)
    - Executive Council/Related Materials 1975/4 (Box 19, Folder 17)
    - Executive Council 1975/6 (Box 19, Folder 18)
    - Executive Council/Minutes and Agenda 1975/11 (Box 19, Folder 19)
    - Executive Council/Related Materials 1975 (Box 19, Folder 20)
    - Executive Council/Conference Call 1975/11 (Box 19, Folder 21)
    - Executive Council/Minutes and Agenda 1976/3 (Box 19, Folder 22)
    - Executive Council/Related Materials I 1976/3 (Box 19, Folder 23)
    - Executive Council/Related Materials II 1976/3 (Box 19, Folder 24)
    - Executive Council 1976/6 (Box 19, Folder 25)
    - Executive Council 1976/11 (Box 19, Folder 26)
    - Executive Council/Correspondence 1977/3 (Box 19, Folder 27)
    - Executive Council/Minutes and Agenda 1977/3 (Box 19, Folder 28)
    - Executive Council/Related Documents I 1977/3 (Box 19, Folder 29)
    - Executive Council/Related Documents II 1977/3 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Executive Council I 1977/6 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Executive Council II 1977/6 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Executive Council/Conference 1977/9 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Executive Council/ Minutes and Agenda 1977/10 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Executive Council/Related Documents 1977/10 (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Executive Council/Related Documents and Reports 1977/10 (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Executive Council/Progress Reports 1977 (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - Executive Council/Minutes and Agenda 1978/3 (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - Executive Council/Related Documents 1978/3 (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - Executive Council I 1978/6 (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - Executive Council II 1978/6 (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - Executive Council 1978/10 (Box 20, Folder 13)
    - Executive Council/Motion of Censure/Walter Nelson-Rees 1978/10 (Box 20, Folder 14)
    - Executive Council 1979 (Box 20, Folder 15)
    - Executive Council 1980 (Box 20, Folder 16)
    - Executive Council 1984 (Box 20, Folder 17)
    - Executive Council 1985 (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Subseries VII.B. Annual Meeting, 1946-1986; 2,000 items (3 linear feet)
    Files containing correspondence, memos, reports, minutes, abstracts, programs, rosters, arranged by date of meeting and then in alphabetical order by subject.
    - Annual [no date] Organization Packet (Box 20, Folder 19)
    - Annual 1946 (Box 20, Folder 20)
    - Annual 1950 (Box 20, Folder 21)
    - Annual 1951 (Box 20, Folder 22)
    - Annual 1952 (Box 20, Folder 23)
    - Annual 1953 (Box 20, Folder 24)
    - Annual 1954 (Box 20, Folder 25)
    - Annual 1955 (Box 20, Folder 26)
    - Annual/Programs and Abstracts 1956 (Box 20, Folder 27)
    - Annual/Reports and Related Documents 1956 (Box 20, Folder 28)
    - Annual 1957 (Box 20, Folder 29)
    - Annual 1958 (Box 20, Folder 30)
    - Annual 1959 (Box 20, Folder 31)
    - Annual 1960 (Box 20, Folder 32)
    - Annual/Programs and Abstracts 1961 (Box 20, Folder 33)
    - Annual/Reports 1961 (Box 20, Folder 34)
    - Annual/Programs and Abstracts 1962 (Box 20, Folder 35)
    - Annual/Reports 1962 (Box 20, Folder 36)
    - Annual/Programs and Abstracts 1963 (Box 20, Folder 37)
    - Annual/Reports and Minutes 1963 (Box 20, Folder 38)
    - Annual/Business Meeting and Programs 1964 (Box 20, Folder 39)
    - Annual/Programs and Abstracts 1964 (Box 20, Folder 40)
    - Annual/Programs and Abstracts 1965 (Box 20, Folder 41)
    - Annual/Reports 1965 (Box 20, Folder 42)
    - Annual/Programs and Abstracts 1966 (Box 20, Folder 43)
    - Annual/Reports and Minutes 1966 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Annual/Programs and Abstracts 1967 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Annual/Reports and Minutes 1967 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Annual/Programs and Abstracts 1968 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Annual/Reports 1968 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Annual/Local Arrangements Committee 1969 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Annual/Photographs 1969 (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - Annual/Program and Exhibit Catalogue 1969 (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Annual/Reports 1969 (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - Annual/Local Committee 1970 (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - Annual/Program and Abstracts 1970 (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - Annual/Publicity Committee 1970 (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - Annual/Publicity Committee 1970 (Box 21, Folder 13)
    - Annual/Reports, Minutes and Related Documents 1970 (Box 21, Folder 14)
    - Annual/Banquet 1971 (Box 21, Folder 15)
    - Annual/Correspondence (1967-1970) 1971 (Box 21, Folder 16)
    - Annual/Correspondence (1971/1-4) (Box 21, Folder 17)
    - Annual/Correspondence (1971/5-1972/6) (Box 21, Folder 18)
    - Annual/Exhibits Committee 1971 (Box 21, Folder 19)
    - Annual/Local Organizing Committee 1971 (Box 21, Folder 20)
    - Annual/Officers and Council 1971 (Box 21, Folder 21)
    - Annual/Organization of Meeting 1971 (Box 21, Folder 22)
    - Annual/Program Committee 1971 (Box 21, Folder 23)
    - Annual/Printed Program and Schedule 1971 (Box 21, Folder 24)
    - Annual/Publicity 1971 (Box 21, Folder 25)
    - Annual/Registration Committee and List of Registrants 1971 (Box 21, Folder 26)
    - Annual/Correspondence 1972 (Box 21, Folder 27)
    - Annual/Organizing Committee, Minutes and Related Documents 1972 (Box 21, Folder 28)
    - Annual/Program 1972 (Box 21, Folder 29)
    - Annual/Correspondence 1973 (Box 21, Folder 30)
    - Annual/Local Committee 1973 (Box 21, Folder 31)
    - Annual/Programs Committee 1973 (Box 21, Folder 32)
    - Annual/Programs and Abstracts 1973 (Box 21, Folder 33)
    - Annual/Local Committee 1974 (Box 21, Folder 34)
    - Annual/Program 1974 (Box 21, Folder 35)
    - Annual/Correspondence 1975 (Box 21, Folder 36)
    - Annual/ Exhibits Committee 1975 (Box 21, Folder 37)
    - Annual/Local Committee 1975 (Box 21, Folder 38)
    - Annual/Program and Abstracts 1975 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Annual/Reports, Minutes and Related Documents 1975 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Annual/Local Committee 1976 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Annual/Program and Abstracts 1976 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - Annual/Correspondence 1977 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Annual/Local Committee 1977 (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - Annual/Correspondence 1978 (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - Annual/Local and Program Committee 1978 (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - Annual/List of Meetings 1970-1978 (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - Annual/Abstracts 1979 (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - Annual/Local Committee 1979 (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - Annual/Local Committee 1980 (Box 22, Folder 12)
    - Annual/Program and Abstracts 1980 (Box 22, Folder 13)
    - Annual 1981 (Box 22, Folder 14)
    - Annual 1982 (Box 22, Folder 15)
    - Annual/Local Committee 1983 (Box 22, Folder 16)
    - Annual 1984 (Box 22, Folder 17)
    - Annual 1985 (Box 22, Folder 18)
    - Annual 1986 (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - Subseries VII.C. Decennial Review Conference, 1956–1976; 1,900 items (2.75 linear feet)
    Organizational files and meeting records containing correspondence, memos, reports, budgets, ledgers, minutes, agendas, proceedings, session papers, programs, and directories are arranged by conference date, then in alphabetical order by subject and then in date order.
    - Decennial Review Conference/ Agenda 1956 (Box 22, Folder 20)
    - Decennial Review Conference/ Proceedings 1956 (Box 22, Folder 21)
    - Decennial Review Conference/ Abstracts and Copies of Papers 1966 (Box 22, Folder 22)
    - Decennial Review Conference/ American Cancer Society Grant 1966 (Box 22, Folder 23)
    - Decennial Review Conference/ Budget 1966 (Box 22, Folder 24)
    - Decennial Review Conference/ Correspondence 1966 (Box 22, Folder 25)
    - Decennial Review Conference/ Directory of Participants and Program 1966 (Box 22, Folder 26)
    - Decennial Review Conference/ Expense Invoices 1966 (Box 22, Folder 27)
    - Decennial Review Conference/ Programs, Announcements and Related Documents 1966 (Box 22, Folder 28)
    - Decennial Review Conference/Prospective Invitees 1966 (Box 22, Folder 29)
    - Decennial Review Conference/Reimbursements of Invited Speakers 1966 (Box 22, Folder 30)
    - Decennial Review Conference/Bank Statements 1976 (Box 22, Folder 31)
    - Decennial Review Conference/Correspondence (1971-1974) 1976 (Box 22, Folder 32)
    - Decennial Review Conference/Correspondence (1975) 1976 (Box 22, Folder 33)
    - Decennial Review Conference/Correspondence/Invitations 1976 (Box 22, Folder 34)
    - Decennial Review Conference/ Correspondence/General 1976 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Decennial Review Conference/ Correspondence/Invitations 1976/2 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Decennial Review Conference/ Correspondence/Invitations List and Requests 1976 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Decennial Review Conference/ Local Arrangements 1976 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - Decennial Review Conference/Mailing 1976/3 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - Decennial Review Conference/ Minutes 1976 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Decennial Review Conference/ National Institute of Health Grant (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - Decennial Review Conference/ Photos of Participants (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - Decennial Review Conference/Program 1976 (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - Decennial Review Conference/Program Committee 1976 (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - Decennial Review Conference/ Registration 1976 (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - Decennial Review Conference/Session 1 Papers 1976 (Box 23, Folder 12)
    - Decennial Review Conference/Session 2 Papers 1976 (Box 23, Folder 13)